是谁出主意 让服务生都穿溜冰鞋的？
Whose idea was it to put everybody in the diner on skates?
某个白痴客人投意见箱的
Some idiot customer put a suggestion in the suggestion box.
天哪，他们盗用我的想法 是你？
-Oh,my God! They took my idea! -That was you?
过去吧
Okay,there you go.
瑞秋，我帮你泡了可可
Rachel,I made you cocoa.
小心…
Oh,that's so....
天哪！你们还好吗？
Oh,my God! Are you guys okay?
喔天呐
Oh,my.
本集播出：“一只鸡一只鸭”
The One With a Chick and a Duck
你留山羊胡有点像撒旦
You know,with that goatee,you kind of look like Satan.
所以神父才会对我洒圣水
So that's why the priest threw holy water on me.
你得开心一点
You have to cheer up.
你应该跟我和罗斯出门
You should come out with Ross and me.
总比整天坐着为凯特伤心好
Anything is better than sitting here crying all day about Kate.
我伤心是因为 没有人相信昆西的理论（《法医昆西》）
I was crying because nobody believed Quincy's theory.
我要上电视了
I'm gonna be on TV!
不会吧
No way!
有一个讨论秘鲁化石的座谈会
They're putting together a panel to talk about the fossils in Peru.
探索频道要去拍摄
The Discovery Channel's filming it!
天哪！谁会看？
Oh,my God! Who's gonna watch that?
谢了，可以走了吗？
Thanks. You ready to go?
我看过一个女生穿那件背心
I saw a girl with that vest.
谢了
Thanks.
大部份的人都视巧克力和篮子 为传统的复活节礼物
Most of us think of chocolate and baskets as traditional Easter gifts.
有些人坚持送活的小鸡
Some people insist on giving live chicks as presents.
不幸的是，大部份的小鸡 都活不到国庆日
Unfortunately,most of these guys won't live to see the 4th of July.
由于照顾得不妥善 它们马上就会死
As a result of improper care,they will be dead.
你们有小鸡吗？
You guys got any of those baby chicks?
我看到电视上的广告 那些小鸡好可爱
I was watching this commercial on TV,and,man,those things are cute!
彼特，你回来了！你看
Pete,you're back! Hey,check this out!
溜冰鞋
Skates!
你比钱德结实，他像纸一样一撞就倒
You're sturdier than Chandler. He crumbled like a piece of paper.
旅途顺利吗？
How was your trip?
你送什么给我？
What'd you bring me?
日本饭店的梳洗用品
Hotel toiletries from Japan!
我要永远保留下来
These are gonna go in my permanent collection.
你知道这上面写的什么吗？德克萨斯出品
You know what that says in English?Made in Texas.
要喝咖啡吗？ 好啊
-Want some coffee? -That'd be great.
普通的还是低咖啡因的？
Regular or decaf?
最近的就行了
Whichever's closest.
问我今天做了什么 你今天做了什么？
-Ask me what I did today. -What did you do today?
我买下一家餐厅 想请你当主厨
I bought a restaurant and I'd like you to be the chef.
他居然要送我一家餐厅
Can you believe he offered me a restaurant?
那个混蛋，你要我踹他吗？
What a jerk. You want me to kick his ass?
从我拥有简易烘烤箱 开了“简易莫妮卡”糕饼店起
It's been my dream since I got my first Easy-Bake Oven...
就在梦想这一天
...and opened Easy-Monica's Bakery.
我死也甘愿，我绝对能胜任
I would kill for this job. I can totally do this job...
我吃的苦头也够多了
...and God knows,I've paid my dues.
但彼特这么做是因为他喜欢我
But Pete's doing this because he has a crush on me.
你对他还是没兴趣？
And you're still not attracted to him at all?
我怎么能接下这个餐厅？ 我不能
How could I accept a restaurant from him? I can't.
七年级时史都文森 送我项链我也没收
I couldn't accept a necklace from Stu Vincent in the 7th grade.
这是两回事 他是你的健康教育老师
But,Mon,that was totally different. He was your health teacher.
怎么了？
What,honey?
被你撞到的地方好痛
My side hurts from when you crashed into me.
天哪，对不起
Oh,God,I'm so sorry.
天哪
Oh,God!
嗨，你们猜怎样？
Hey,you guys. Guess what?
你在内河船上找到工作？
Got a job on a riverboat?
我一整年没穿这套西装 因为你不喜欢
I didn't wear this suit for a year,because you hated it.
你不是我的女朋友了，所以…
You're not my girlfriend anymore,so....
我懂了，你想要强调
I see. This suit is making a point.
你现在孤家寡人 可以尽情的出丑
Now that you're on your own,you're free to look as stupid as you'd like.
你喜欢这套西装吧？
You like it,right?
当然，你穿起来比桑德斯上校穿好看多了（肯德基创始人）
I like it even more on you than I did on Colonel Sanders.
罗斯，开玩笑的，回来
Ross,I'm kidding. Come here.
你要说什么？
What were you gonna tell us?
-你发明轧棉机的过程？ -好吧，再见
-Was it how you invented the cotton gin?-Okay, goodbye.
-刚才是不是有点太苛刻了 -开什么玩笑
-Was that a little harsh?-Are you kidding?
记得你穿那件灰色运动服吗
Remember when you used to wear that gray sweat suit.
我还曾叫你兴登堡呢（1937年爆炸的德国飞艇）
And l used to call you the Hindenberg.
不记得  我错了
No. My mistake
你投书到意见箱之后
So after you put the suggestion in the box...
多久才得到回应？
...how long did it take for it to happen?
大约三个月
About three months.
所以离上身裸露的决定 大约还有两星期
So I guess that's about two weeks before the topless thing kicks in.
我买了一个东西 打开来看
I got you something. Open it! Open it!
是一只鸡
It's a chicken.
很可爱吧？
It's cute,huh?
两位，你们了解鸡吗？
You guys? Do you know anything about chicks?
家禽？不了解
Fowl? No.
女人？不了解
Women? No.
养鸡是重责大任
They are a huge responsibility.
尤其是小鸡 需要无微不至的照顾
Especially at this age. They require constant care.
它们不能吃错东西 需要很多关爱
They need just the right food and lots and lots of love.
这个没问题
Well,no problem there.
轻一点，连尼（创办了室内宠物饲养的人）
Easy,Lenny.
你考虑过了吗？
So,I mean,have you thought about it?
是这样的
Okay,here's the thing.
我讨厌“是这样的”
Not "the thing." I hate "the thing."
是怎样的？
What's "the thing"?
我不能接受
I can't do it.
抱歉，我也很想接受
I'm sorry. I wish I could...
但你对我有特殊情感
... but you have these feelings for me.
你在担心这个？
That's what you're worried about?
如果是这个问题 那就没问题了
If that's the problem,we've got no problem.
我正打算吃饭时告诉你 我这趟出国认识了一个人
I was gonna tell you over dinner,but I met somebody else,on my trip.
她叫安，是记者 我们在飞机上认识
Her name's Ann. She's a journalist. We met on the plane.
她想把我的花生吃完
She wanted to finish off my peanuts.
我听成别的（花生与阴茎谐音） 我们大笑一场
I thought she said something else. We had a big laugh.
我等烦了
I got tired of waiting.
太好了 抱歉，但我好为你高兴
That's great. I'm sorry,but I'm so happy for you.
我可以为你工作了 看来可以了
-Now I can work for you! -I guess you can.
天哪，太棒了
Oh,my God! This is incredible!
你猜怎样？ 我要溜进办公室去辞职
You know what? I'm gonna roll right into that office and quit!
好
All right!
推一下，好吗？
Could you give me a little push?
祝你好运
Good luck!
我要辞职了
I'm quitting!
我没事，我很好
I'm okay! I'm all right!
真叫人兴奋啊 你去日本，编造了一个女人
That's exciting. You went to Japan,made up a woman.
什么？
What?
我是说这个女人… 是虚构的吧？
I'm just saying,this "woman," I mean,she's fictitious,no?
为什么这么说？ 你还是喜欢莫妮卡
-Why would you say that? -You're still into Monica.
你谎称认识别人 好让她为你做事
You said there's somebody else so she'd work with you.
相处久了，也许就会产生感情
If you spend time together,maybe something might happen.
你真行
You're good. You're good.
我只是直觉准，还会通灵
No,I'm fairly intuitive. And psychic.
很实在的天赋
It's a substantial gift.
请答应我不要告诉她
Can you promise me that you won't tell her?
没问题，我答应你 告诉她什么？
Absolutely. I promise. Tell her what?
谢谢你
Thanks a lot.
我是认真的 我的直觉很准，但记性很差
No,I'm serious. I'm intuitive,but my memory sucks.
好吧，但这是最后一次
Okay,but this is the last time.
这里吱，那里吱
With a chick-chick here And a chick-chick there
这里吱，那里吱 到处都在吱吱叫…
Here a chick,there a chick Everywhere a chick-chick
鸡…
Chicken....
她好吗？
How's she doing?
她？
She?
你不觉得是她吗？
Don't you think it's a she?
我不知道
I don't know.
看不出来，那个东西 一下子就缩回去了
I can't tell. Whatever it was went back in too quickly.
我要换衣服 我要去跟其他演员喝酒
I gotta change. I'm meeting some of the cast for drinks.
什么？
Excuse me?
怎么了？
What?
你排练时，我留在家里
I stayed home while you were at rehearsal...
好陪着我们的小鸡
...so somebody could be here with our chick.
是谁从半夜两点撑到五点？
Who was up from 2:00 this morning until 5:00...
好哄她睡觉？
...trying to get her back to sleep?
你以为我没起来吗？
You don't think I get up when you get up?
又来了
Oh,here it comes.
没错，又来了 我整天困在这里
Yes! Here it comes! I'm stuck here all day!
你才回来陪了我们几秒钟
And then you come in and spend two seconds with us...
就要出去跟朋友花天酒地？
...and then expect to go off gallivanting with your friends?
这样不行喔，先生
Well,I don't think so,mister!
我需要轻松一下 我工作了一整天
I need to relax,okay? I was working all day.
照顾我们的小鸡就不是工作？
And you don't think taking care of our chick is work?
我不是那个意思，我是说…
That's not what I said. I just meant
我知道你想说什么
I know what you meant!
你有没有发现，自从有了小鸡
Did you notice that ever since we got this chick...
我们争吵的次数变多了？
...we've been fighting a lot more than we used to?
也许我们还不适合养小鸡
I don't know,maybe we weren't ready to have a chick.
-虽然有时我确实想要一个的 -我知道，我知道
l sure want one someday though.l know. l know.
我明天送它回去
I'll take her back tomorrow.
三块钱会退吗？
We'll get our $3 back?
-不敢相信你们还这样 -我们要把她还回去了
-l can't believe you still have that.-We're taking her back.
不，我是说你们脸上的可笑表情
No, that ridiculous thing on your face.
-谢谢 -好的
-Thank you.-All right?
我两小时后要录影 请你们帮个忙
I have that TV thing in two hours,and I need your help.
怎么样？蓝色还是棕色的好？
What do you think? This blue suit or this brown one?
棕色可以突显你的眼睛
The brown one brings out your eyes.
但蓝色那套让你的屁股很翘
But your butt looks great in the blue one.
真的？
Really?
阿司匹林舞还真有效
That aspirin dance really works.
你还是… 我没事
-ls that still...? -I'm fine.
你有事 我没事
-No,you're not! -Yes,I am.
我很好，看我的
Look,I'm fine. Watch. Look at that.
你得去看医生，好吗？
You've got to go to a doctor,okay?
我要去我老板家参加晚宴
I have to get ready and go to a dinner at my boss's house.
有几个人非见不可
There's people there that I have to meet.
你一定会令人印象深刻 “你好，我是瑞秋格林”
I'm sure you'll make a great impression. "Hi,I'm Rachel.
“很高兴认识你”
It's nice to meet you."
你的肋骨可能断了
Come on,you probably have a broken rib.
我明天再去医院，它还是断的
I'll go to the hospital tomorrow. It'll still be broken then.
但我打扮时需要帮忙
But you know,I could use a hand getting ready.
你不帮忙就走
Either help me,or go.
好，我走
Fine. I'll go.
走之前能不能先帮忙？
But before you go,could you help me first?
好，我帮
Sure. I'll help you.
你们在啊 要怎么把小鸡弄出录影机？
Good! Do you guys know how to get a chick out of a VCR?
你知道吗？我不会用左手化
You know what? I cannot do this with my left hand.
你能不能也帮我化妆？
Would you please help me with this too?
用这一支好了
Let's use this brush.
这个？ 小心一点
-This stuff? -Careful.
沾一点
Light.
在眼睑上刷一下就好 刷一下
Just sweep it across the lid. Just sweep it.
对不起
Sorry!
你是在戳我的眼睛
That's just poking me in the eye.
对不起，闭上…
I'm sorry. Close....
刷一下就好 我在刷
-Just sweep it. -I'm sweeping.
刷、刷…
Sweep,sweep....
刷均匀，不要…
Now make it even,because we don't....
不要太多，隐隐约约就好
I don't want it to be too much. I want it to be subtle.
你的妆不够浓
You don't wear enough of this.
你几时觉得我的妆不够浓了？
Since when do you think I don't wear enough of this?
闭上眼睛，你一定会喜欢
Close your eye. You're gonna like this better....
闭眼睛 吹一下
-Close,close. -Blow it.
这样看起来比较成熟
Because I think this will make you a little more sophisticated.
跟妓女一样成熟？
Sophisticated like a hooker?
你猜我今晚要做什么？ 什么？
-Guess what I'm doing tonight. -What?
我要跟彼特去看餐厅
I'm checking out the restaurant with Pete.
莫妮卡，我好替你兴奋
Monica,I am so excited for you!
我有一件事要告诉你
I have to tell you something.
什么事？
What?
我不能告诉你
I can't tell you.
告诉我你能告诉我的，不是更容易吗
Wouldn't it be easier to tell me something that you could tell me?
是的，在完美世界里
Well,sure,in a perfect world.
我答应不说 我对所有神明发过誓
But no. I promised I wouldn't tell,and I swore to all my Gods.
跟罗斯和瑞秋有关吗？
Does it have to do with Ross and Rachel?
跟乔伊有关吗？
Does it have to do with Joey?
跟钱德和他 床边的袜子有关吗？
Does it have to do with Chandler and that sock he keeps by his bed?
不是，不过你待会儿要告诉我
No,but let's come back to that later.
好了，够美了吧？
There you go! Good enough for your party?
是啊
Sure.
是啊，我会坐在采购部那个变性人旁边
Sure. I'll just sit next to the transsexual from purchasing.
我得走了，祝你晚宴愉快
All right,I gotta go,So good luck at the party.
再帮我换一下衣服好吗？
Could you just stay and help me get dressed?
当然好
Sure.
太好了，转过去吧
Great. Okay,just turn around.
什么？
What?
我不想让你看到我的身体
I don't want you to see me naked.
我看过几万遍了 我在你身上吃热奶油
I've seen you naked a million times. I ate hot fudge off you naked.
我从你的肚脐眼吸出小软糖
I sucked that mini-marshmallow out of your bellybutton.
那个不一样，我们那时在交往
Yeah,but that was different. We were going out then.
现在很奇怪
Now it's weird.
我随时都能看到你的裸体
Rach,you know,I can see you naked anytime I want.
什么？
What?
我只需要闭上眼睛，你看
All I have to do is close my eyes. See?
罗斯，别闹了
Ross,stop that!
拜托，别再那样想我了
Come on! Don't think of me like that anymore.
抱歉，你管不到
Sorry. Nothing you can do about it.
这是前任男友的权利
It's one of my rights as the ex-boyfriend.
别闹了，够了
Stop it! Cut it out! Cut it out!
对不起，我不会再…
I'm sorry. It will never happen
等一下
Wait a minute! Wait,wait....
现在有一百个你，我是国王
Now there are 100 of you,and I'm the king!
成熟一点，这又没什么
Would you grow up? It's no big deal.
好吧
All right. Fine.
很好，我决定自己换衣服
See what you did? I'm gonna be doing it by myself now.
天哪，听我说
Oh,my God. All right,look,look....
小心，你得去医院，好吗？
Easy. Easy. You have to go to the hospital,okay?
我真的得去了
I do. I really do.
我去帮你拿外套，再送你上车
I'll get your coat,then I'll put you in a cab.
你不陪我去吗？
You're not gonna come with me?
当然要
Of course I am.
我得先打个电话
I just have to make a call.
谢谢
Thank you.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
对不起，我不能这样去医院
I'm sorry. I just can't go to the hospital looking like this.
跟旅行有关吗？
Does it involve travel?
跟木屐有关吗？
Does it involve clogs?
木屐还是爪子？
Clogs or claws?
木屐
Clogs.
爪子？
Claws?
所以不是罗斯和瑞秋 也不是钱德和乔伊
So it doesn't involve Ross or Rachel or Chandler or Joey.
那彼特呢？  不是
What about Pete? No
怎么样？
What is it?
彼特怎么了？ 我不知道
-What about Pete? -I don't know!
我好像在跟灵犬莱西说话（英国作家艾瑞克莫布里奈特的作品）
I feel like I'm talking to Lassie.
菲比，你就直说好吗？ 不行啦
-Phoebe,would you just tell me? -I can't!
我得走了 但是很接近了
-I gotta go. -But you're so close!
跟彼特的电脑公司有关吗？
Something to do with Pete's company?
你走吧，你死也猜不到的
Go! You'll never get it!
我知道
I know.
没错，那就是杰丝敏布丽丝（《海滩游侠》）
See,yes. That's Yasmine Bleeth.
她是一种完全不同的“鸡”
She's a completely different kind of chick.
你们两个我都爱
I love you both.
是非常不一样的爱
But in very different ways.
你在干什么？不是要送她走？
What are you doing? You were gonna take her back.
我有，但是店里不收
I did. But the store wouldn't take her back.
我带她去收容所 你猜我发现什么？
Then I took her to the shelter. You know what I found out?
要是找不到人领养 就要杀了她
If they can't find a home for her,they kill her!
我绝不让小杰丝敏惨遭毒手
I won't let that happen to little Jasmine.
很好，其实我也有点反悔
Good,good,because I was kind of having second thoughts too.
不只小鸡，所有的动物都一样
And it's not just chicks. It's all kinds of other animals.
太可怕了，你做得对
That's horrible. You did the right thing.
谢了，你这么想就好
Thanks. I'm glad you see it that way.
好有趣的故事
Funny story!
真不敢相信
I don't believe this!
你看这个冰柜，好巨大
Look at this refrigerator! It's gigantic!
我可以住在里面 会冷，不过我本来就很冷
I could live in this thing! I'd be cold,but I'm always cold!
是传统火炉 我最喜欢传统火炉了
Oh,my God! Look at these spider burners! I love spider burners!
你喜欢？
So you like it?
太完美了，真谢谢你
It is so perfect! Thank you so much.
不客气
You're welcome.
你刚才在闻我的头发？
Did you just smell my hair?
怎么可能，没有啊
No! No way! What?
天哪 怎么了？
-Oh,God. -What?
你对我还是有感觉
You still have feelings for me.
我只是对餐厅的事很兴奋
I'm just excited about the restaurant,that's all.
我爱你，有这么糟吗？
I love you. Is that so bad?
不糟，一点也不糟
No,it's not bad. It's not bad at all.
其实很好
It's really nice.
会受伤的人是我 我都不介意了
The only one who stands to get hurt is me,and I'm okay with that.
你或许不介意受伤
You may be okay with getting hurt...
我却不能当那个伤你的人
...but I am not okay with being the one who hurts you.
所以我不能接受这份工作
That's why I can't take this job.
什么？
What?
我们也不该再见面了
We probably shouldn't see each other anymore.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你如果真的这么想，那好吧
I mean,if that's really what you want,okay.
很抱歉，事情…
I'm sorry things
你先闭嘴，让我确认一下
Shut up for a second and let me just see something.
你有说实话吗？
You'd tell me the truth?
X光片看起来怎么会胖
Rach,you can't look fat in an x-ray.
你给我在这里好好反省
Now you stay out here and you think about what you did!
那是一只鸭子 一只坏鸭子
-That's a duck! -That's a bad duck!
今晚的事顺利吗？
How'd the thing go tonight,Ross?
什么事？
What thing? What thing?
没什么，博物馆有事 走吧
Nothing. There was this thing at the museum. Come on.
小心
Easy.
等你回来，希望你记住 小鸡不是玩具
Now,when you come back,I hope you remember that that chick is not a toy!
到底是什么事？
What "thing"? What is this "thing"?
我今晚本来要上探索频道
I was kind of supposed to be on TV tonight for the Discovery Channel.
天哪
Oh,my God!
罗斯，你为什么不说？
Ross,why didn't you tell me that?
我一说，你就会让我去
I knew that if I told you,you'd make me go...
我知道你今晚 需要有人陪着，来吧
...and I knew you needed someone to be with you tonight. Come on.
我真不敢相信 怎么了？
-I cannot believe you. -What?
你对我太好了
That is the sweetest thing.
你该睡觉了
You should get some sleep.
抱歉搞砸你的今晚
Sorry I spoiled your evening.
你没事就好
As long as you're okay.
明天见
So I'll see you tomorrow.
再见
See you.
你做了什么？
What did you do?
你们在干什么？
What you doing?
游泳
Having a swim.
小鸡呢？
What about the chick?
鸡不会游泳
Chicks don't swim.
确定？
Are you sure?
不晓得
I don't know.
要试试看吗？ 好啊
-Should we try? -Sure.
看吧，我就说它不会游
See,I told you. They don't swim.
再等一下
Well,give him a minute.
好，宝贝，没事了
It's okay. It's okay,baby,baby,baby.